Woodland
The Farm
The Grid Arrives
Longacre Square
Horsecars
The Carriage Trade
The First Theatre
The Hotel on the Triangle
Digging
The Tower
The Subway
The First Ball
Electric Signs
Automobiles
Wartime
Prohibition
The Great White Way
Peak Bulbs
The Zipper
The Crash
Burlesque
Grind Houses
Swing
The Fair Year
The Dimout
Wartime Crowd
The Lights Come Back
Postwar
Neon
Bigger Boards
Cinemascope
Chrome
Stripped
White Marble
Fraying
Grind
The Low Point
Blackout Summer
Bottom
Hoardings
Demolition
Empty Lots
Cleanup
The Theatres Return
Screens On The Tower
Millennium Bright
Full Colour
The Canyon
Chairs In The Road
The Plazas
Wraparound
Peak Crowd
Empty
Coming Back
Normal
Present Day
Layers of Light
The Green Canyon
The Screens Go Dark
The Last Frame